<resource>
  <string name="title" lang="en">#@CCKCs.NET Blog io HK</string>
  <string name="description">
    #@CCKCs.NET Blog io HK, which launched in 2026, is a individualise blog directed to sharing the blogger’s life, skills, and dreams. It highlights individuality, dedication, and future career plans. 
    Furthermore, it offering readers insight into the blogger’s journey and aspirations.
  </string>
  <string name="AbstractContextView1" id="cvAbstract1" lang="en">
    #@CCKCs.NET Blog io HK, which launched at 2026 in GitHub, is a individualise HTML/CSS/JS Blog web site page specializing in sharing a life and showcasing the future career of a person who are the bloger
    and contributing a long-term future plan also the dream of a person. The blog also offer a gateway to let the others can know more about how the person are and the skill, knowledge, dedication 
    also the wishes of the blogger have.
  </string>
  <string name="WelcomeTitle" id="tWel" lang="en">Welcome to visit '#@CCKCs.NET Blog io HK' !!!</string>
  <string name="WelComeContextView1" id="cvWel1" lang="en">
    '#@CCKCs.NET Blog io HK' which was a blog-LIKE HTML/CSS/JS + XML web site page created by Cyrus CHUI (FULL: CHUI KA CHUN) who a hongkonger and intrestd in programing of software & system, also web & API developing. 
    Additionally, who just aged 1X, in HD-y1 study Sem-3 of Software Engeering (SE) at HKIIT@VTC and as a memeber in HK-Scout HKI-Region 82nd Scouts (Venture). Furthermore, who want to take part in IT industry to be a
    vocational programmer, then be advanced programmer, then developer, then advanced developer, then engine, then advenced engine, then assoc-chief engine, then chief engine, then designer, then advanced designer, then 
    climbing higer and higher ...
  </string>
  <string name="WelcomeContextView2" id="cvWel2">( -- to be continue ... -- )</string>
  <string name="_ContextView_" id="cv__"></string>
  <author name="director">cyruschuikc[cyruschuikc-kamisatokira@outlook.com]</author>
  <copyright lang="en">&copy;All copyrights belongs to cyruschuikc(kamisato.kira) 2026 ~ -</copyright>
</resource>
